lovetheatre.com 2017-11-24

# Security | Information | LOVEtheatre

LOVEtheatre (we) are proudly owned and operated by The Ticket Machine Group Ltd, a company registered in England (company number 026389710). Please read this privacy policy carefully, as it describes what personal information we collect and how we use it. 

What information do we collect?

We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order or subscribe to our newsletter. 

Any data we request that is not required will be specified as voluntary or optional. 

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number or credit card information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously. 

What do we use your information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: 

\- To personalize your experience   
(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs) 

\- To improve our website   
(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you) 

\- To improve customer service   
(your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs) 

\- To process transactions   
Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested by the customer. 

\- To send periodic emails 

The email address you provide for order processing, will only be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order or request. 

If you decide to opt-in to our mailing list, you will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. 

Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email. 

How do we protect your information?

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or access your personal information. 

These security measures include: password protected directories and databases to safeguard your information, SSL (Secure Sockets Layered) technology to ensure that your information is fully encrypted and sent across the Internet securely or PCI Scanning to actively protect our servers from hackers and other vulnerabilities. 

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.

After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.

Do we use cookies?

Yes. Cookies are small text files that are placed on your computer by websites that you visit or certain emails you open. They are widely used in order to make websites work, as well as to provide business and marketing information to the owners of the site. You can manage and/or delete these small files as you wish. To learn more about cookies and how to manage them, visit www.aboutcookies.org.

The Ticket Machine Group Ltd uses cookies for the following purposes:

Functionality

We use a cookie to keep track of your 'login' status on several of our websites. As an example, if you have signed up as a member of LOVEtheatre, we will use a cookie to remember if you are currently logged in. This helps in the following ways:

1\. you don't have to keep signing in on every page  
2\. we can automatically sign you out after a period of inactivity (which helps keep your personal information secure)

Tracking

We use Google Analytics cookies to collect information about how visitors use this site and when issues are encountered (such as broken links). Google analytics stores information about what pages you visit, how long you were on the site, how you got here and what you click on. We do not store your personal information so this information cannot be used to identify who you are.    We do not allow Google to use or share our data.

We use Google Analytics to make sure our website is meeting our users’ needs and to help prioritise improvements. Google provides more details on the [Google privacy and cookie policy page](http://www.google.co.uk/intl/en/policies/privacy/). Google also provides a [browser add-on](http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout) which allows you to opt out of Google Analytics across all websites.

Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

If you've given your consent when registering for your personal information to be provided to carefully selected third parties they may contact you by post, telephone or email with information or offers regarding their goods and services.  
LOVEtheatre and its associated companies will not share your data with any third parties without your consent, except under the following circumstances: 

  1. trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or providing services to you on our behalf, so long as those third parties agree, in writing, to keep this information confidential;. 
  2. when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property, or safety; and 
  3. non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to third parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses

California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

As part of the California Online Privacy Protection Act, all registered users of our site may make any changes to their information at anytime by signing in to their account and editing their details.

Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

CAN-SPAM Compliance

We have taken the necessary steps to ensure that we are compliant with the CAN-SPAM Act of 2003 by never sending out misleading information.

Online Privacy Policy Only

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

Terms and Conditions

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at LOVEtheatre.com.

Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.

Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below. Policy changes will apply only to information collected after the date of the change.   
This policy was last modified on: 28th July 2011 

Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below. 

The Ticket Machine Group Ltd  
First Floor,   
39-41 Charing Cross Road,   
Leicester Square,   
London,   
WC2H 0AR,   
United Kingdom  
techsupport@ticketmachinegroup.com  
+44 (0) 20 7420 9730 

Privacy Policy Customer Pledge

We pledge to you, our customer, that we have made a dedicated effort to bring our privacy policy in line with the the following important privacy laws and initiatives:  
Federal Trade Commision Fair  
California Online Privacy Protection Act  
Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act  
Privacy Alliance  
Controlling the Assault of Non-Solicited Pornography and Marketing Act

If at anytime you have a cause that needs to be disputed please fill out the [Trust Guard Dispute Resolution form](http://secure.trust-guard.com/disputesystem/).   
**  
**
